myeway.com 2019-04-10

# Legal - eWAY Australia

Web Active Corporation Pty Ltd ABN 32 086 209 403 trading as “eWAY” (eWAY) regards customer privacy as an important part of our relationship with our merchants and partners. eWAY is bound by the Privacy Act 1988 (as amended) and the Australian Privacy Principles (collectively, Privacy Law). The following privacy policy applies to all eWAY users,and sets out the way in which eWAY collects and uses personal and corporate information, and other requirements as set out in the Privacy Law.

**Last Updated:**  25 May 2015

### COLLECTION OF INFORMATION

In order to use the eWAY Payment Gateway (eWAY), we require certain personal and corporate information relating primarily to Your internet merchant facility (including Your merchant number, terminal ID and/or settlement account, depending on Your Merchant Bank).

We collect corporate information, including your company name, website, email address, type of business and ABN.

We collect personal information such as your name, email address, telephone number, address, credit card information and date of birth.

The information we collect (whether personal or corporate) is collected in one or more of these ways:

  * through disclosure of such information by you through eWAY’s website;
  * over the phone to an eWAY representative; or
  * from a third party engaged by you (such as a web developer).

  1. 

Where information is provided to us by a third party engaged by you, we are typically only provided with your name, phone number and/or email address.

We collect personal and corporate information for the purpose of providing you with eWAY’s payment gateway product and a high level of customer service.

Any communication with us (regardless of mode) is recorded and stored in order to provide service references, ensure compliance with our service standards and to assist in our staff training and development initiatives.

### REGISTRATION

In order to use this Website, you must first complete the registration form and create a username and password. During registration you must provide us with certain personal information (such as name and Email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest.

You have the option to provide company demographic information (such as industry type and business size) to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you with a more personalised experience on our site. eWAY is the sole owner of the information collected on eway.io/hk. eWAY collects personal information from our users at several different points on our Website.

### USE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

When we collect your personal or corporate information, we use that information to:

  * establish an eWAY account and a merchant account at a financial institution – this may include us providing your personal and corporate information with a financial institution;
  * manage an existing payment gateway and merchant relationship;
  * engage in direct marketing to you (in any medium);
  * testimonials and client/ partner listings on our website and within marketing materials; and
  * inform third parties other than financial institutions who provide us services – we do not however provide personal information to such third parties, without your prior consent.

Where we disclose your personal or corporate information to third parties, it is solely for the purpose of such third parties establishing your merchant account and processing payments, unless otherwise stated.

We have subsidiaries in the UK, New Zealand, U.S.A. and Canada and so we may disclose your personal and corporate information to recipients in these regions. We may notify you, by amending this privacy policy or otherwise, should we disclose any personal information to any other jurisdiction. If we notify you of such disclosure, we will advise you of the country in which the overseas recipient is located.

#### ORDERS

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personal information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, Email, and postal address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

#### COOKIES

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s technical information.  In general, we use the information that is collected through the use of cookies on our Site to make the Site more useful to you and to tailor your experience with us and our communications with you to meet your special interests and needs.

Some of the ways in which we use cookies may include the following:

  * When you register for any of eWAY’s services, we use cookies to make it easier for you to navigate through and complete the registration form.
  * When you login to MYeWAY, we use cookies to easily authorise your credentials as you navigate through our secure pages.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site, such as our administration area, may be limited.

  * Some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to, or control over, these cookies.
  * This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by this site only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third party, whether or not affiliated with eWAY.

#### COMMUNICATIONS

eWAY uses your personal information for essential communications, such as confirmation Emails, accounts information, and critical service details. We may also use this information for other purposes, including direct marketing. If at any time you wish not to receive such correspondence, you may request to be removed from any mailing lists by emailing us at [compliance@eway.io](mailto:compliance@eway.io).

#### THIRD PARTIES

We use third parties to provide the essential links between the merchants, the banks and ourselves in order to provide credit card payment gateway services on our site. When you sign up for eWAY, we will share your Internet Merchant Account details as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

eWAY does not share any information with third parties for any unknown or unrelated uses.

#### CLEAR GIFS (WEB BEACONS /WEB BUGS)

Our third party advertising partner, such as Google Adwords and third party tracking utility partners may employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

To learn more about our advertising company’s use of clear gifs, please go to [https://adwords.google.com](https://adwords.google.com/)

#### FORUM

If you use the eWAY forum on this site, you should be aware that any personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in these forums.

#### LEGAL

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required or permitted by law (including Privacy Law) and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

#### TESTIMONIALS

We may post customer testimonials on our website which may contain personal information such as the customer’s name. We will obtain your consent to use your personal information prior to posting the testimonial. If at any time you no longer wish to have any testimonial you have provided posted on the website you may request for it to be removed by emailing us at [compliance@eway.io](mailto:compliance@eway.io).

#### PARTNER’S DIRECTORY

eWAY provides free-of-charge a directory for associated partners to join. eWAY associated partners generally include third party applications that contribute to the functionality of the Gateway Services. The process of registering for the partner directory is initiated and completed entirely by the partner, with all information submitted by the partner. If at any time the partner feels that they no longer wish to be a part of this directory they can request to be removed by e-mailing us at [compliance@eway.io](mailto:compliance@eway.io).

#### LINKS AND OTHER EWAY SITES

There are many external links on the eWAY site. The terms and conditions set out in this privacy statement only cover sites operated by eWAY, which include [eway.io/hk](https://eway.io/hk), au.myeway.com and quote.eway.com.au .

### STORAGE OF COLLECTED INFORMATION

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can email us at [compliance@eway.io](mailto:compliance@eway.io "eWAY Compliance").

### ACCESS TO COLLECTED INFORMATION

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on the Your Profile page in the eWAY Administration Area or by emailing our Customer Support at [compliance@eway.io](mailto:compliance@eway.io "eWAY Compliance") or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

### COMPLAINTS

If you wish to lodge a complaint about our handling of your personal information or our compliance with our privacy policy or Privacy Law, you may lodge the complaint by emailing our Customer Support at [compliance@eway.io](mailto:compliance@eway.io "eWAY Compliance") or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

We will contact you to acknowledge your complaint as soon as possible after receiving your complaint. We will investigate your complaint and provide you with a written response. If we are unable to resolve your concern, you may request an independent person to investigate your complaint, such as the Privacy Commissioner.

### CHANGES TO PRIVACY POLICY

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by Email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

**eWAY**  
Web Active Corporation  
Level 1, 2 Shea Street,  
Phillip ACT 2606  
AUSTRALIA

Email: [compliance@eway.io](mailto:compliance@eway.io "eWAY Compliance")
